[
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 18 and height 45?",
      "correctAnswer": "405.0",
      "options": [
        "402.5",
        "405.0",
        "409.0",
        "407.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 10 and height 12?",
      "correctAnswer": "60.0",
      "options": [
        "57.5",
        "60.0",
        "64.0",
        "62.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 27 and height 22?",
      "correctAnswer": "297.0",
      "options": [
        "301.0",
        "299.5",
        "297.0",
        "294.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 45 and height 44?",
      "correctAnswer": "990.0",
      "options": [
        "987.5",
        "994.0",
        "990.0",
        "992.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 48 and height 6?",
      "correctAnswer": "144.0",
      "options": [
        "141.5",
        "148.0",
        "144.0",
        "146.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 41 and height 27?",
      "correctAnswer": "553.5",
      "options": [
        "557.5",
        "551.0",
        "556.0",
        "553.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 43 and height 26?",
      "correctAnswer": "559.0",
      "options": [
        "561.5",
        "556.5",
        "559.0",
        "563.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 11 and height 20?",
      "correctAnswer": "110.0",
      "options": [
        "107.5",
        "114.0",
        "112.5",
        "110.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 22 and height 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "44.0",
      "options": [
        "41.5",
        "48.0",
        "44.0",
        "46.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 11 and height 12?",
      "correctAnswer": "66.0",
      "options": [
        "68.5",
        "66.0",
        "70.0",
        "63.5"
      ]
    }
]